I love holidays!
我热爱假期！
There’s nothing better than jetting off to a foreign destination to visit the attractions it has on offer.
没有什么比搭乘飞机前往异国他乡，游览当地的特色景点更惬意的事了。
Of course, I’m not alone.
当然，并非只有我这么想。
Millions of people are doing the same, and why not?
成千上万的人都在做着同样的事，为什么不呢？
The world has an amazing variety of must-see sights, from breathtaking natural scenery to impressive old cities.
世界上有各种各样不容错过的景观，从令人惊叹的自然风光到宏伟的古城。
But the problem is that too many of us are visiting them at the same time, putting pressure on these delicate and ancient places.
但问题在于，太多人选择在同一时间前往这些地方，给这些脆弱而古老的景点带来了巨大压力。
That’s why a number of beauty spots and historic sites have been introducing charges or restrictions on the tourists who visit.
这也是为什么许多风景名胜和历史古迹开始对游客收取费用或设置游览限制。
There are many reasons for this: to reduce overcrowding, which can spoil the ambience of a place, to manage wear and tear on old crumbling buildings, to tidy up the mess that visitors leave behind, or – as some may suggest – creating tourist traps to make more money out of the visitors.
这么做的原因有很多：缓解拥挤——毕竟拥挤会破坏氛围；减少对老旧建筑的损耗；清理游客留下的脏乱垃圾；或者，正如有些人猜测的那样，打造“旅游陷阱”来从游客身上榨取更多利润。
The famous Italian city of Venice with its picturesque canals has, for example, introduced an entry fee of up to €10 for short-stay tourists.
以拥有如画运河的意大利名城威尼斯为例，该市已开始向短途游客征收最高10欧元的入城费。
Venetians have long complained that mass tourism is swamping the city.
威尼斯人长期以来一直抱怨，大规模的旅游业正在淹没这座城市。
Now, passengers arriving by cruise ship will have to pay a ‘landing tax’ which Mayor Luigi Brugnaro says, “would generate much-needed income to keep the city clean.”
如今，乘坐游轮抵达的游客还需要缴纳“上岸税”，市长路易吉·布鲁尼亚罗表示，这笔税款“将为城市保洁工作带来急需的收入”。
Many cities in Europe already charge an occupancy tax on tourists who stay in hotels and guest houses.
欧洲的许多城市早已开始对入住酒店和民宿的游客征收住宿税。
In the UK, Edinburgh is hoping to do the same, controversially making it the first city in the country to do so.
在英国，爱丁堡市也计划推行这项政策，这一举措颇具争议，若落地，爱丁堡将成为英国首个征收游客住宿税的城市。
This levy, that is usually charged per person per night of accommodation, raises money to help protect the environment, pay for infrastructure, or promote tourism.
这种税费通常按每人每晚的住宿费来收取，所筹集的资金将被用于环境保护、基础设施建设或旅游业推广。
In Italy’s capital city, Rome, new laws are being introduced to clampdown on bad tourist behaviour, which some argue is spoiling the look and feel of the city.
在意大利首都罗马，政府出台了新法规来打击不文明的游客行为——有人认为这类行为正在破坏这座城市的风貌。
Rules include banning drinking water from fountains and attaching ‘love padlocks’ to bridges.
新规包括禁止饮用喷泉里的水，以及禁止在桥上悬挂“爱情锁”。
As more of us can now afford to travel, tourist destinations are going to get busier, so maybe new laws and taxes are going to be a necessary part of the sightseeing experience.
随着越来越多的人有能力外出旅行，旅游目的地会变得愈发拥挤，或许新的法规和税费政策，将成为观光体验中必不可少的一部分。